George Lardner Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part I: Subject File, 1923-1997 (Box 1-285)
  - Watergate Affair
    - Tapes
      - Halperin v. Kissinger, 1974, undated
      - In re Grand Jury Subpoena Duces Tecum, 1973-1974, (4 folders)
      - Nixon v. Sampson, 1974-1975 (Box 271)
      - Nixon v. Sirica, 1973, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes (Box 272)
        - Miscellaneous, 1972-1974, undated
        - Notebooks
          - 1973-1974, (7 folders)
          - Undated (Box 273)
      - Research material
        - Legal documents
          - Exhibits, 1971-1973, undated
          - Miscellaneous, 1973-1974, undated
        - Miscellaneous, 1973-1974, (4 folders)
        - Newspaper clippings and related material, 1972-1979, undated, (3 folders)
      - U.S. Senate Select Committee on Presidential Campaign Activities v. Nixon, 1973-1974, undated, (6 folders) (Box 274)
      - United States v. Mitchell (74-128), 1974-1975, undated (Box 275)
      - United States v. Nixon, 1973-1974, (2 folders)
    - Wallace, George C., 1973, undated
  - Wedtech
    - Biaggi, Mario
      - Articles, 1987-1988
      - Research material
        - Newspaper clippings and related material, 1986-1989, undated
        - Press releases, 1987-1988
    - Castellano, Vito J.
      - New York v. Castellano, legal documents, undated
      - Research material, newspaper clippings, and related material, 1987
    - Chinn, W. Franklyn
      - Articles, 1987
      - Research material
        - General, 1979-1983, undated
        - Newspaper clippings and related material, 1987-1988
      - United States v. Wallach
        - Legal documents
          - Exhibits, 1985-1986, (2 folders)
          - Grand jury indictment outline, 1987 (Box 276)
    - General
      - Articles, 1986-1988
      - Interviews, 1987-1988
      - Notes, 1986-1988, undated, (3 folders)
      - Research material
        - Bankruptcy proceedings
          - Bear, Stearns & Co., underwriters, 1986-1987
          - In re Wedtech Corp., legal documents, 1986-1987
          - Wedtech Corp. v. London, legal documents, 1987
          - Wedtech Corp. v. Pinkhasov, legal documents, 1987
        - Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 277)
        - Newspaper clippings and related material, 1982-1989, undated
        - Press releases, 1985-1987
        - U.S. Senate Committee on Governmental Affairs, Subcommitte on Oversight of Government Management
          - “Oversight of Federal Procurement Decisions on Wedtech”
            - Hearings
              - Documents, 1982-1986
              - Published proceedings, 1987
                - Part 1, Role of the Small Business Administration
                - Part 2, Role of the Navy
            - Levin, Carl, statements, 1987
            - Press release, 1988
          - Pollner, Martin R., statement by counsel, Wedtech Corp., 1987
          - “Wedtech: A Review of Federal Procurement Decisions,” report, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 278)
          - Witness list and statements, 1987-1988, (2 folders)
    - Guariglia, Anthony
      - Articles, 1988
      - New York v. Guariglia, legal documents, 1987
      - Research material, newspaper clippings, and related material, 1988
    - London, R. Kent, research material, newspaper clippings, and related material, 1987
    - Meese, Edwin
      - Articles, 1987-1988
      - Notes, 1987-1988
      - Research material, newspaper clippings, and related material, 1986-1988, undated
    - Merola, Mario, research material, newspaper clippings, and related material, 1986-1988
    - Mitchell, Clarence M., legal documents, 1987 (Box 279)
    - Mitchell, Parren J.
      - Articles, 1987
      - Research material
        - Correspondence, 1981-1987
        - Press releases, 1986
    - Moreno, Mario
      - Articles, 1988
      - New York v. Moreno, legal documents, 1987-1988
      - Research material, newspaper clippings, and related material, 1987-1988
    - Neuberger, Fred
      - New York v. Neuberger, legal documents, 1987
      - United States v. Neuberger, legal documents, 1987
    - Shorten, Lawrence
      - New York v. Shorten, legal documents, 1987
      - Research material, correspondence, 1987
    - Simon, Stanley, 1988
    - United States v. Biaggi
      - Legal documents
        - Appeal, 1988
        - Exhibits, defendant's, 1982-1985
        - Grand jury indictments, 1987, (2 folders)
        - Notice of motion, 1988
        - Prospective juror questionnaire, undated
        - Transcripts, 1988
        - Transcripts, 1988, (6 folders) (Box 280)
        - Transcripts, 1988, (5 folders) (Box 281)
        - Verdict sheet, undated
      - Notes, 1988, (5 folders) (Box 282)
    - Wallach, E. Robert
      - Articles, 1985-1989
      - Bert v. Wallach
        - Legal documents, 1983-1986
        - Research material, newspaper clippings, and related material, 1986-1987
      - Interviews, 1987
      - Notes, 1988, undated (Box 283)
      - Rebney v. Wells Fargo Bank and Abascal v. Crocker National Bank, legal documents, 1987, (2 folders)
      - Research material
        - Article by Wallach, 1970
        - Correspondence, 1981-1987
        - Financial disclosure, 1986
        - Newspaper clippings and related material
          - General, 1976-1986, undated
          - Wedtech, 1987-1989
      - Wedtech v. Wallach, legal documents, 1987
  - Wiretaps and electronic surveillance
    - Articles and notes, 1975, undated
    - Research material, 1974-1976, 1985, undated
  - Yablonski family murders and United Mine Workers complicity
    - Articles, circa 1970
    - Notes
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1970
      - Notebooks, circa 1970, (3 folders) (Box 284)
    - Research material
      - Legal documents and miscellany, 1956, 1967-1970, undated
      - Newspaper clippings and related material, 1966-1974, (3 folders) (Box 285)
  - Yuba City, Calif., murders
    - Articles, circa 1971
    - Notes, circa 1971
    - Research material, 1971
  - Zaccaro, John, and Geraldine Ferraro, 1984-1985, undated
- Part I: Miscellany, 1963-1995 (Box 285-288)
  Correspondence, newsletters, directories, financial records, and notes.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of organization and document type and chronologically thereunder.
  - Catholic University of America, Washington, D.C., Communications Committee, 1979-1980, undated (Box 285)
  - Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild
    - 1969-1975
    - 1976-1979, undated, (5 folders) (Box 286)
  - Washington Post Co.
    - Address and telephone directories, 1974-1986, undated
    - Administrative papers, 1967-1990, undated
    - Expense accounts, 1972-1979, 1987-1995, undated, (4 folders) (Box 287)
    - General correspondence
      - 1963-1977, (6 folders)
      - 1978-1992, undated, (3 folders) (Box 288)
    - Notes and tips, 1967-1985, undated
- Part I: Oversize, 1980 (Box OV 1)
  List of campaign receipts and expenditures.
  Arranged and described according to the series, container, and folder from which the item was removed.
  - Subject File (Box OV 1)
    - Campaign spending, 1984 national election campaigns
      - Reagan-Bush reelection campaign
        - Federal Election Commission, selected list of receipts and expenditures, 1980 (Container 9)
- Part I: National Security Classified Information, 1961-1963 (Box CL 1)
  Research material
  Arranged and described according to the series, containers, and folders from which the items were removed.
  - Central Intelligence Agency (Box CL 1)
    - Goodwin, Richard, assassination plots in Latin America
      - Research material, 1961-1963 (Container 22), (2 folders)
- Part II: Subject File, 1959-2005 (Box 289-560)
  Writings, drafts, notes, interviews, correspondence, and research material including newspaper clippings, printed matter, reports, photographs, legal documents, financial records, congressional hearing records, and other government documents.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Biden, Joseph R., 1993-2000 (Box 289)
  - Boorda, Jeremy Michael, 1996, (3 folders) (Box 289)
  - Bush, George W. (Box 289)
    - Bush, Barbara, and Jenna Bush, 1999-2001 (Box 289)
    - Bush, George H. W., and Jeb Bush, 1992 (Box 289)
    - Business career, 1981-1999, (3 folders) (Box 289)
    - Business career, 1981-1999, (4 folders) (Box 290)
    - Campaign donors, 1978-2001 (Box 290)
    - Card, Andrew H., 1992-2001, (2 folders) (Box 290)
    - Cheney, Richard B., 2000 (Box 291)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1999, (2 folders) (Box 291)
    - Daily activities, 2000-2001, (2 folders) (Box 291)
    - Drafts, 1999, (2 folders) (Box 291)
    - Drunk driving, 1990-2000, (2 folders) (Box 292)
    - Financial disclosure, 1991-1997, (3 folders) (Box 292)
    - First Son: George W. Bush and the Bush Family Dynasty, manuscript by Bill Minutaglio, 1998 (Box 292)
    - First Son: George W. Bush and the Bush Family Dynasty, manuscript by Bill Minutaglio, 1998 (Box 293)
    - General, 1967-2000, (6 folders) (Box 293)
    - General, 1967-2000, (7 folders) (Box 294)
    - General, 1967-2000, (6 folders) (Box 295)
    - General, 1967-2000, (7 folders) (Box 296)
    - General, 1967-2000, (6 folders) (Box 297)
    - General, 1967-2000, (2 folders) (Box 298)
    - Harken Energy Corp., 1982-2000, (5 folders) (Box 298)
    - Harken Energy Corp., 1982-2000, (5 folders) (Box 299)
    - Indices, circa 1999 (Box 299)
    - Interview notes, 1999-2002 (Box 299)
    - Interview notes, 1999-2002 (Box 300)
    - The Kinkaid School, Piney Point Village, Tex., 1997-1999 (Box 300)
    - Latsis, Yiannis, yacht, 2000 (Box 300)
    - Maps, 1999 (Box 300)
    - Miscellany, 1967-2000, (3 folders) (Box 300)
    - "Nomadic years," 1973-1999 (Box 301)
    - Oil industry, 1981-1982, (2 folders) (Box 301)
    - Opposition research, 1982-1994, (2 folders) (Box 301)
    - Presidential appointments (Box 301)
      - Chao, Elaine L., 2001 (Box 301)
      - Chao, Elaine L., 2001, (4 folders) (Box 302)
      - Chavez, Linda, 1987-2001, (4 folders) (Box 302)
      - Chavez, Linda, 1987-2001, (3 folders) (Box 303)
      - Evans, Donald Louis, 2000-2001, (2 folders) (Box 303)
      - General, 2001-2002 (Box 303)
      - Martinez, Mel, 2001 (Box 303)
    - Profile notes, 1999, (3 folders) (Box 304)
    - Profiles, 1988-1999 (Box 304)
    - Pull for Youth Foundation, 1973-1982 (Box 304)
    - Rainwater, Richard, 1996-1999 (Box 304)
    - Rainbo Club, Inc., Athens, Tex., 1986-1999, (2 folders) (Box 304)
    - Rainbo Club, Inc., Athens, Tex., 1986-1999, (3 folders) (Box 305)
    - Republican Attorneys General Association, 1998-2000, (3 folders) (Box 305)
    - Rove, Karl, 1987-2002, (6 folders) (Box 306)
    - Rove, Karl, 1987-2002, (6 folders) (Box 307)
    - Spectrum 7, 1982-1985 (Box 307)
    - Spectrum 7, 1982-1985 (Box 308)
    - Tax havens, 2001, (2 folders) (Box 308)
    - Texas Air National Guard, 1968-2001, (3 folders) (Box 308)
    - Texas Air National Guard, 1968-2001, (4 folders) (Box 309)
    - Texas governorship (Box 309)
      - Children's Health Insurance Program, 1998-1999 (Box 309)
      - Children's Health Insurance Program, 1998-1999, (4 folders) (Box 310)
      - General, 1996-2000, (2 folders) (Box 310)
      - General, 1996-2000, (2 folders) (Box 311)
      - Lawrence Littwin v. GTECH Corp., 1997-1999, (2 folders) (Box 311)
      - Texas Lottery Commission and GTECH Corp., 1993-1999, (3 folders) (Box 311)
      - Texas Lottery Commission and GTECH Corp., 1993-1999, (7 folders) (Box 312)
      - Texas Lottery Commission and GTECH Corp., 1993-1999, (3 folders) (Box 313)
      - Tort reform, 1986-1999, (4 folders) (Box 313)
      - Tort reform, 1986-1999, (5 folders) (Box 314)
      - Tort reform, 1986-1999, (7 folders) (Box 315)
      - Tort reform, 1986-1999 (Box 316)
    - Texas Rangers (baseball team), 1982-1999, (3 folders) (Box 316)
    - Vietnam, 1968-1999 (Box 316)
    - Yale University, New Haven, Conn., 1968-1993 (Box 316)
  - Cairo, Illinois, civil rights violations, 1967-1969 (Box 316)
  - Campaign finance (Box 316)
    - Campaign contributions ("Big checks"), 2000 (Box 316)
    - Campaign contributions ("Big checks"), 2000, (5 folders) (Box 317)
    - Clinton-Gore reelection campaign (Box 317)
      - Asian Pacific Advisory Council (APAC), 1996, (2 folders) (Box 317)
      - Asian Pacific Advisory Council (APAC), 1996, (6 folders) (Box 318)
      - Asian Pacific Advisory Council (APAC), 1996, (3 folders) (Box 319)
      - Bossie, David N., 1998 (Box 319)
      - Burton, Dan, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 319)
      - Chung, Johnny, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 319)
      - Chung, Johnny, 1998 (Box 320)
      - Clippings, 1998 (Box 320)
      - Contributions, 1997, (2 folders) (Box 320)
      - General reference, 1996-1998 (Box 320)
      - Hubbell, Webster, tapes, 1996, (4 folders) (Box 320)
      - Hubbell, Webster, tapes, 1996, (4 folders) (Box 321)
      - Independent counsel memoranda, circa 1998, (3 folders) (Box 321)
      - Independent counsel memoranda, circa 1998, (5 folders) (Box 322)
      - Immunity, 1997, (3 folders) (Box 322)
      - Immunity, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 323)
      - Lum, Nora T., and Gene H. K., 1997 (Box 323)
      - Miscellany, 1996 (Box 323)
      - Radek, Lee J., independent counsel law, 2000, (2 folders) (Box 323)
      - Reno, Janet, 1998, (4 folders) (Box 323)
      - Reno, Janet, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 324)
      - Trie, Yan Lin, "Charlie," 1998, (2 folders) (Box 324)
      - Wu, Irene, 1998, (3 folders) (Box 324)
    - Clinton, Hillary Rodham (Box 324)
      - Leadership political action committees, 2001 (Box 324)
      - Leadership political action committees, 2001, (2 folders) (Box 325)
      - Use of Air Force jet during Senate campaign, 1999-2000 (Box 325)
    - Federal Election Commission (Box 325)
      - Brochures, 1987-1996 (Box 325)
      - Coalition investigation, 2001, (2 folders) (Box 325)
    - "Follow the Dollar" Common Cause report, 2001 (Box 325)
    - Gore, Al (Box 325)
      - Fund raising, 2000 (Box 325)
      - Glicken, Howard, 1999-2000 (Box 325)
      - Glicken, Howard, 1999-2000, (8 folders) (Box 326)
      - Internal Revenue Service Freedom of Information Act request, 2000, (2 folders) (Box 326)
      - Internal Revenue Service Freedom of Information Act request, 2000 (Box 327)
      - Occidental Petroleum Corp., 2000 (Box 327)
      - Probes, 2000 (Box 327)
      - Special counsel recommendation, 2000, (5 folders) (Box 327)
      - Specter, Arlen, hearing, 2000 (Box 328)
      - Union Zinc, Inc., 2000 (Box 328)
    - Issue advertisements, 1997 (Box 328)
    - National Right to Life Political Action Committee, 2000 (Box 328)
    - Republican Party fund raising, 2001, (2 folders) (Box 328)
    - Starr, Kenneth, Independent Counsel, 1995-1997, (3 folders) (Box 328)
  - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA) (Box 329)
    - Agee, Philip ( CovertAction ), 1978-1980 (Box 329)
    - Angleton, James, 1975 (Box 329)
    - Articles, 1975-1980, circa 1989 (Box 329)
    - Budget, 1989-1991, (6 folders) (Box 329)
    - Bush, George H. W., 1976-1991 (Box 329)
    - Bush, George H. W., 1976-1991 (Box 330)
    - CIA Information Act of 1984, 1983-1984, (4 folders) (Box 330)
    - Charter (Box 330)
      - Angola operations, 1978 (Box 330)
      - Articles, 1976-1979 (Box 330)
      - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 330)
      - Executive order summaries, 1978, (2 folders) (Box 330)
      - First Principles analysis, 1976-1978 (Box 331)
      - "Friendly" spies, 1978 (Box 331)
      - Interview notes, 1978, (2 folders) (Box 331)
      - Legislation, 1978 (Box 331)
      - Miscellany, 1978 (Box 331)
      - Notes, circa 1978 (Box 331)
      - Reform, 1978-1979 (Box 331)
      - Security and Intelligence Fund, 1978 (Box 331)
      - Surveillance, 1978 (Box 331)
      - Testimony before Congress, 1978, (5 folders) (Box 332)
    - Clippings, 1974-1975, (2 folders) (Box 332)
    - Colby, William E. (Box 332)
      - Death and legacy, 1996 (Box 332)
      - Public appearance after dismissal, 1975 (Box 332)
      - Testimony, 1975 (Box 332)
      - Testimony, 1975, (2 folders) (Box 333)
    - Commission on CIA Activities within the United States (Rockefeller Commission), 1975, (2 folders) (Box 333)
    - Correspondence and leads, 1975-1982, 1991-1993 (Box 333)
    - Food shortages, 1974, (2 folders) (Box 333)
    - Ford, Gerald R., administration, 1974-1975, (2 folders) (Box 333)
    - Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act of 1976, 1976, (2 folders) (Box 333)
    - Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act of 1976, 1976 (Box 334)
    - Foreign relations of the U.S., 2001 (Box 334)
    - Freedom of Information Act (Box 334)
      - Reform, 1981 (Box 334)
      - Requests, 1983-1993 (Box 334)
      - Washington Post Co. v. Central Intelligence Agency, 1986-1988, (2 folders) (Box 334)
    - Gates, Robert Michael, 1987-1993 (Box 334)
    - Global Marine, Inc., 1975 (Box 334)
    - Guatemala, territory dispute with Belize, 1968-1975 (Box 334)
    - Hills, Roderick M., 1975 (Box 335)
    - House Assassinations Committee records breach, Regis Blahut snooping acquisition, 1979, (2 folders) (Box 335)
    - Hughes, Howard, Glomar Explorer (submarine), 1974-1975, (5 folders) (Box 335)
    - Indices for studies and reports, circa 1979 (Box 335)
    - Intelligence Commission work plan, 1995 (Box 335)
    - Intelligence Identities Protection Act (Box 335)
      - Article drafts, 1980-1981 (Box 335)
      - Dear Colleague letters, 1980-1981 (Box 335)
      - Legislation, 1980-1981, (2 folders) (Box 336)
      - Miscellany, 1981-1982 (Box 336)
      - Notes, 1979-1981, (3 folders) (Box 336)
      - Press and clippings, 1979-1981 (Box 336)
      - Statements before Congress, 1980-1981, (3 folders) (Box 336)
      - Whip advisories, 1980-1981 (Box 336)
    - Katzenbach, Nicholas, circa 1975 (Box 336)
    - Marchetti, Victor, 1975-1976 (Box 336)
    - Miscellany, 1973-1992 (Box 337)
    - Notes, circa 1975-circa 1989, (4 folders) (Box 337)
    - Research material, 1961-1991, (4 folders) (Box 337)
    - Roselli, John, Cuban Project (Operation Mongoose), 1975, (2 folders) (Box 337)
    - Schweiker, Richard, 1975 (Box 338)
    - Select Committee on Intelligence (Box 338)
      - Miscellany, 1975-1977 (Box 338)
      - Nedzi Committee, 1975, (5 folders) (Box 338)
      - Pike Committee, 1975 (Box 338)
    - Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities (Church Committee) See also Container 459, Church Committee (Box 338)
      - Assassination plots on foreign leaders (Box 338)
        - Castro, Fidel, 1961-1977, (3 folders) (Box 338)
        - Diem, Ngo Dihn, 1975 (Box 339)
        - Lumumba, Patrice, 1960, 1975, (3 folders) (Box 339)
        - Miscellany, 1961, 1975 (Box 339)
        - Report release, 1975, (2 folders) (Box 339)
        - Trujillo, Rafael, 1961-1975, (2 folders) (Box 339)
      - General, 1975-1976 (Box 339)
      - Mail intercepts, 1975 (Box 339)
      - Mail intercepts, 1975 (Box 340)
      - Toxins, 1975, (3 folders) (Box 340)
    - Soviets (Box 340)
      - General, 1991 (Box 340)
      - Golitsyn, Anatoly, 1991 (Box 340)
      - Kalugin, Oleg, 1992, (4 folders) (Box 340)
    - Sturgis, Frank, 1975, (2 folders) (Box 340)
    - "Task Force Report on Greater CIA Openness," 1991-1992, (3 folders) (Box 341)
    - Webster, William H., 1989-1991, (4 folders) (Box 341)
    - Webster, William H., 1989-1991, (3 folders) (Box 342)
  - Chennault, Anna, 1981-1997 (Box 342)
  - Clinton, Bill (Box 342)
    - FBI files flap ("Filegate") (Box 342)
      - Anderson, Mari, 1996, (2 folders) (Box 342)
      - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 342)
      - FBI General Counsel report, 1996 (Box 342)
      - General, 1996, (2 folders) (Box 342)
      - General, 1996, (8 folders) (Box 343)
      - General, 1996, (7 folders) (Box 344)
      - General, 1996, (8 folders) (Box 345)
      - General, 1996, (7 folders) (Box 346)
      - General, 1996, (7 folders) (Box 347)
      - General, 1996 (Box 348)
      - Index, 1996 (Box 348)
      - Livingstone, Craig and Lisa Wetzl, 1996, (2 folders) (Box 348)
      - Notes and clippings, 1996-1998, (4 folders) (Box 348)
      - Press and clippings, 1996-1998 (Box 348)
      - Sharpiro, Howard, misconduct charge, 1997 (Box 348)
      - U.S. House of Representatives interim report, 1996, (2 folders) (Box 349)
      - U.S. Senate hearing, 1996, (3 folders) (Box 349)
      - White House records released, 1996, (2 folders) (Box 349)
    - Impeachment, 1998 (Box 349)
    - Impeachment, 1998 (Box 350)
    - Lewinsky, Monica S., affair. (Box 350)
      - Bakaly, Charles G., 2000 (Box 350)
      - Brill, Steven and leaks, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 350)
      - Clinton, Bill, and women, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 350)
      - Goldberg, Lucianne, 1998, (4 folders) (Box 350)
      - Goldberg, Lucianne, 1998, (9 folders) (Box 351)
      - Jones, Paula, 1997 (Box 351)
      - Secret Service and David Hale, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 352)
      - Secret Service privilege, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 352)
      - Starr, Kenneth, background, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 352)
      - Tripp, Linda, 1997-1999, (4 folders) (Box 352)
      - Tripp, Linda, 1997-1999, (3 folders) (Box 353)
    - Presidential spending, 1992 (Box 353)
    - Press and clippings, 1993-2001, (4 folders) (Box 353)
    - Travel, 2001 (Box 353)
    - U.S. Air Force crash, Dubrovnik, Croatia, 1996 (Box 353)
    - Weekly Compilation of Presidential Documents, 1996 (Box 353)
    - White House Counsel, 1996, (2 folders) (Box 353)
    - White House Counsel, 1996 (Box 354)
    - White House Database, 1996 (Box 354)
    - White House email inquiry (Box 354)
      - Class action lawsuit, 2000, (3 folders) (Box 354)
      - General, 2000, (2 folders) (Box 354)
      - General, 2000, (10 folders) (Box 355)
      - Gore, Al, data and document dump, 2000, (7 folders) (Box 356)
      - Legal documents, 2000 (Box 356)
      - Memorandum of understanding, 2001 (Box 356)
      - Witnesses, 2000, (2 folders) (Box 356)
      - Witnesses, 2000, (2 folders) (Box 357)
    - White House gifts and property dispute, 2001, (6 folders) (Box 357)
    - Whitewater inquiry, 1997-1998 (Box 358)
  - DeBartolomeis, Silvio J., 1992 (Box 358)
  - Declassification (Box 358)
    - Interagency Security Classification Appeals panel, 1997-1998, undated (Box 358)
    - Lyndon Baines Johnson Library, Austin, Tex., correspondence, 1975-1978, (2 folders) (Box 358)
    - Research material (Box 358)
      - Clinton, Bill, executive order, 1993-1998, (3 folders) (Box 358)
      - Defense Authorization Act, 1998-2004, (3 folders) (Box 359)
      - Garfinkel, Steven, 1999 (Box 359)
      - Government secrecy, 1998 (Box 359)
      - State Department Chile Declassification Project, 1999-2000, (2 folders) (Box 359)
      - National Security Archive, Washington, D.C., Henry Kissinger records release, 1999-2001 (Box 359)
  - Defense Intelligence Network, 1992 (Box 359)
  - Domestic and family violence (Box 360)
    - Bureau of Justice statistics, 1991-1998, (2 folders) (Box 360)
    - Campus crimes, 1996-2000, (2 folders) (Box 360)
    - Center City, Philadelphia, Pa., rapes, 1997-2001, (2 folders) (Box 360)
    - Child abuse, 1995-2000 (Box 360)
    - Clinton, Bill, statements, 1994-1997 (Box 360)
    - Conferences, 1993-1999, (2 folders) (Box 361)
    - Crimes, general, 1993-2000, (3 folders) (Box 361)
    - Gun control, 1993-1998 (Box 361)
    - Index and notes, circa 1996 (Box 361)
    - Juvenile justice, 1994 (Box 361)
    - Lardner, Kristin, murder by Michael Cartier (Box 361)
      - Articles, 1993 (Box 361)
      - Memorial fund, 1993-1994 (Box 362)
      - Notes, 1992-1997 (Box 362)
      - Reader responses, 1995-1998 (Box 362)
      - Speaking engagements, 1993-1996, (5 folders) (Box 362)
      - Speaking engagements, 1995-1998, (7 folders) (Box 363)
      - Speaking engagements, 1999-2000, (6 folders) (Box 364)
      - Speaking engagements, 2000, (3 folders) (Box 365)
      - The Stalking of Kristin, book review, 1995 (Box 365)